casinosnodepositbonuses.com 2015-11-09

# Privacy Policy | Best Casino Bonus BLog

**Privacy policy**

The privacy of our users is a priority number one for us. In this document we will outline what information we gather and comment on our purposes. You are presupposed to read the document carefully before you use our site or submit any personal information as using our site means you admit our privacy policy agreement and bear responsibility. You are also obliged to regularly review the privacy policy as we reserve the right to modify and improve it to maintain our site.

**Information we collect**

Similar to a plenty of other Websites , casinobonusescodes.com uses some log files and stores personal information that you trust us while registration. The information inside log files encloses users IP addresses, types of browsers, data/time stamps, referring/exit pages and number of clicks to analyze trends, manage the site, monitor user’s movement around the site and gather demographic information.

As we mentioned we also store users names, passwords, email addresses, all information needed to log in our site and confirm your identity entering it. We don’t share, sell or disclose any of your email, username and password to any other companies, the third parties or some other outside resources unless it is at the written consent from the users. Our site also use cookies technology to monitor your social behavior

**Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.

**Children’s Privacy**

Under-aged persons are forbidden to register, create accounts and use our site. Before creation of account at our site you are required to check the age declaration of your country, region etc. and verify whether you meet minimum age requirement.

**Distribution of Information**

Haven’t purposed any marketing aims we can share information with governmental organizations under the condition that it is permitted or required by law, aiming help in prevention or protection from fraud or illegal transactions or helping in investigation of already committed fraud.

**Links to other websites**

Our website encloses links to other websites of interest. We don’t bear any kind of responsibility for content or actions of the last, so you use these links at your own risk. Pay attention that we are not liable of protection and privacy of any information you provide at such sites as they are not ruled by this privacy policy. Which implies that you need to read the privacy statement of a used site before exercising it.

more...
